[Music]
ICICI PDL MC is
one of the second largest mutual funds among the leading mutual funds of the country, in a
way it is the second largest mutual
fund, so let me tell you about this, the
IPO is open from today,
first understand what are the positives of ICICI Pidential AMC, it is a very
strong brand, ICICI Pidential
Mutual Fund
also has a big advantage of being a group company of ICICI Bank.  And the
best part is that despite being a group company,
only 9% of their overall business comes from ICICI Bank customers.  That means the
business model is diversified.  It is
not dependent only on ICICI Bank that only ICICI
Bank will sell its products and only its
customers will deposit money.  This is a very good
point.  Highly experienced and long
serving team.
Nimish Shah Sahab since 17-18 years and S Narendra Sahab since 20 years are
such experienced and good
professionals who are in their management team.  It has a
very strong presence.  It is in the
equity segment with a market share of more than 13%.  It is
in the equity segment.
13% is not less in the whole of India.  And if it is
in the hybrid segment then it is the leader.  They alone hold 25% of the
business in the hybrid segment.  The
dominance is complete.   There
are more than 140 schemes.  More than 1.5 crore
investors, you can imagine
how big the base is.  1.5 crore investors
invest new.
Yes,
5 crore investors have Rs 1.5 crore in total mutual funds.   There are
also larger multiples.  But still it is a
diversified business model.  And now PMS,
alternate funds etc. will help in bringing more growth
and giving good margins.  The
track record of growth
and profitability so far is amazing.
is fantastic.  It is an asset model.  There is no need to invest much.
Cash flow is very strong.
EBITDA is 73%.  It's amazing.  Operating
margin and efficient ROE
will look at return on equity.  86 to 87% which
is the best in the industry.  Apart from this, Best of the
Best Funds
FI are the best investors who have been
in pre-IPO and also came in the anchor book yesterday.
Whoever's name you think of will appear in it.
Meaning, everyone has to buy proof of ICICI shares
before the IPO and the good thing
that they did is the
track record of ICICI Bank till now.
Whatever IPOs of their subsidiaries have come till now,
they have kept very tight valuations.
This is the first such IPO and that is why I am
praising it wholeheartedly.  Their
valuations are cheaper than other peers.
They have kept the valuations cheap by about 10 to 15%.  This is a
great job.  And for this I
also congratulate the management team.
What is negative?  The entire offer is for sale.  The
company is not getting any money.  Well,
they don't even need it.
Business is dependent on the stock market and it is for everyone.  Now there
is nothing new in that.  Any specific
negative TR rules that may be a little tighter will have a
slight impact on the expense ratio.  They will
put it on everyone.  It won't make much difference.   The
competition is very high.
Small players are more worried about competition.  ICC
is less.  So overall these are called negatives.  It is of
no use.  There are a lot of positives.
My view at this point in time is that this is
a compounding growth story for India.
It shows the changing patterns of investors in our economy.
It is a must have portfolio stock.   A
must have in your portfolio.  You
can invest in ICIC pro mutual fund IPO for both good listing gains and long term.  My opinion is
crystal clear.
[music]